(futuristic hip-hop beat)
♪ One, two ♪
♪ One, two, three ♪
♪ Yeah, inslumnational, underground ♪
♪ Thunder pounds when I
stomp the ground (woo) ♪
♪ Like a million elephants
or silverback orangutans ♪
♪ You can't stop a train ♪
♪ Who want some? Don't come unprepared ♪
♪ I'll be there, but when I leave there ♪
♪ Better be a household name ♪
♪ Weather man tellin'
us it ain't gon' rain ♪
♪ So now we sittin' in a
drop-top, soakin' wet ♪
♪ In a silk suit, tryin' not to sweat ♪
♪ Hit somersaults without the net ♪
♪ But this'll be the year
that we won't forget ♪
♪ 1-9-9-9, Anno Domini, anything goes ♪
♪ Be whatchu wanna be ♪
♪ Long as you know consequences
are given for livin' ♪
♪ The fence is too high to jump in jail ♪
♪ Too low to dig, I might
just touch hell, hot ♪
♪ Get a life, now they on sale ♪
♪ Then I might cast you a spell ♪
♪ Look at what came in the mail ♪
♪ A scale and some Arm & Hammer ♪
♪ Soul-gold grill and a baby mama ♪
♪ Black Cadillac and a pack of Pampers ♪
♪ Stack of question with no answers ♪
♪ Cure for cancer, cure for AIDS ♪
♪ Make a... wanna stay on tour for days ♪
♪ Get back home, things are wrong ♪
♪ Well, not really, it was bad all along ♪
♪ Before you left adds
up to a ball of power ♪
♪ Thoughts at 1,000 miles per hour ♪
♪ Hello, ghetto, let your brain breathe ♪
♪ Believe there's always mo', ow ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (yeah, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (yeah, uh) ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (ha, ha, ha, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (ha, ha, ha, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad ♪
♪ Uno, dos, tres, it's on ♪
♪ Did you ever think a
pimp rock a microphone? ♪
♪ Like that there Boi and
will still stay street ♪
♪ Big things happen every time we meet ♪
♪ Like a track team, crack
fiend, dyin' to geek ♪
♪ Outkast bumpin' up and down the street ♪
♪ Slam back, Cadillac,
'bout five... deep ♪
♪ 75 emcee's freestylin' to the beat ♪
♪ 'Cause we get crunk,
stay drunk, at the club ♪
♪ Should have bought an
ounce, but you copped a dub ♪
♪ Should have held back,
but you throwed the punch ♪
♪ 'Spose to meet your girl
but you packed a lunch ♪
♪ No D to the U to the G for you ♪
♪ Got a son on the way
by the name of Bamboo ♪
♪ Got a little baby
girl, four year, Jordan ♪
♪ Never turn my back on my kids for them ♪
♪ Should have... it, quit it, rag-top ♪
♪ Before you re-up, get a laptop ♪
♪ Make a business for
yourself, boy, set some goals ♪
♪ Make a fat diamond out of dusty coals ♪
♪ Record number four, but we on a roll ♪
♪ Hold up, slow up, stop, control ♪
♪ Like Janet, Planet, Stankonia's on ya ♪
♪ Movin' like Floyd, comin'
straight to Florida ♪
♪ Lock all your windows,
then block the corridors ♪
♪ Pullin' off my belt 'cause
a whipping's in order ♪
♪ Like a three-piece fish
before I... your daughter ♪
♪ Yo quiero Taco Bell,
then I hit the border ♪
♪ Pitty-pat rappers
tryin' to get the five ♪
♪ I'm a microphone fiend
tryin' to stay alive ♪
♪ When you come to ATL,
boy, you betta not hide ♪
♪ 'Cause the Dungeon
Family gon' ride, ha ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (ha, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad (uh, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad
(y'all heard me, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad, yeah ♪
♪ Don't pull the thang out,
unless you plan to bang ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad
(y'all heard me, yeah) ♪
♪ Don't even bang unless
you plan to hit something ♪
♪ Bombs over Baghdad ♪
(guitar playing over hip-hop beat)
♪ Bombs over Baghdad, yeah ♪
(record scratching)
♪ B-I-G B-O-I ♪
(percussion and guitar playing
over record scratching)
♪ Bob your head, rag-top ♪
♪ Bob your head, rag-top (one, two) ♪
♪ Bob your head, rag-top
(one, two, three, let's go) ♪
♪ Power music, electric revival ♪
♪ Power music ♪